{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20is%20the%20largest%20continent%20by%20land%20area%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Asia",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Africa",
        "North%20America",
        "South%20America"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20smallest%20continent%20by%20land%20area%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Australia",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Europe",
        "Antarctica",
        "Asia"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20ocean%20is%20the%20largest%20by%20area%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Pacific%20Ocean",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Atlantic%20Ocean",
        "Indian%20Ocean",
        "Southern%20Ocean"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20is%20the%20second%20largest%20ocean%20by%20area%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Atlantic%20Ocean",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Indian%20Ocean",
        "Pacific%20Ocean",
        "Arctic%20Ocean"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20largest%20island%20in%20the%20world%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Greenland",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Madagascar",
        "Borneo",
        "New%20Guinea"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20is%20the%20largest%20lake%20by%20surface%20area%20in%20the%20world%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Caspian%20Sea",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Lake%20Superior",
        "Lake%20Victoria",
        "Great%20Bear%20Lake"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20longest%20river%20in%20the%20world%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Nile%20River",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon%20River",
        "Yangtze%20River",
        "Mississippi%20River"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20is%20the%20tallest%20mountain%20in%20the%20world%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Mount%20Everest",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "K2",
        "Kangchenjunga",
        "Lhotse"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20largest%20desert%20in%20the%20world%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Sahara%20Desert",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Arabian%20Desert",
        "Gobi%20Desert",
        "Kalahari%20Desert"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20continent%20has%20the%20most%20countries%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Africa",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Asia",
        "Europe",
        "North%20America"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
